Looking for a home that isn't [music]
cookie cutter? This stunning property in
Belton, Texas's Three Creeks community
sits on a massive halfacre culde-sac
[music] lot, has been beautifully
crafted with custom selections, and is
just minutes from Still House Hollow
Lake. [music] Listed at 474900,
it's the type of home that buyers wait
for, and it just hit the market.
Hey, I'm Andrea Dudik and today I'm
giving you a personal tour of my newest
listing [music] in the Three Creeks
community. Now, some of the reasons that
make this community so desirable are
[music] a its location. You are about 20
minutes from Fort Hood. You're just 50
[music] minutes to an hour north of
Austin, 40 minutes south of Waco, and
[music] 20 to 25 minutes from Temple,
Texas if you're looking to be near the
hospitals or anything in that area.
[music]
Another couple reasons are you're so
close to Still House Hollow Lake. I'm
talking less than 5 minutes if you want
to do anything out there. And this is
one of the only communities with walking
trails. And it also has a pavilion and a
stream. And there's just so much to do
here. Um, so I'm really excited to give
you a tour of this home. I think you're
going to love it. Let's [music] get
started.
From the moment you pull up, this home
has so [music] much curb appeal. The
cutest front porch, elevated
landscaping, and a feeling of privacy
you don't usually get in a community
setting. [music] It's tucked away and
feels super secluded from the rest of
the neighborhood.
Inside, it's bright, [music] open, and
beautifully laid out. The open concept
design makes every inch count, and the
flow of the living, [music] kitchen, and
dining spaces feels intentional and
spacious. It was built in 2022, [music]
but honestly, it feels brand new. All
right, we are in the formal dining
[music] space right off of the entrance
of the home. This home in general, it
was built in 2022. [music]
It's over 2500 square ft, 4 bed,
2 and 1 half bath
with this [music] formal dining space
and again on that awesome halfacre
culde-sac lot. This community in general
has a ton of homes and phases [music]
and they're all very separated, but
where this one is is very private and
secluded and you can really feel that
when you're here. Um, a lot of these
homes out here, you know, you have your
big production builders that build in
bulk. You can sometimes get that cookie
cutter feel and then you have some more
of the smaller builders that build in
less volume. So, the buyers are able to
get more of a custom feel, and that's
exactly what these buyers [music] did.
They picked the floor plan, they made
the selections, and it is so beautiful
and [music] very tastefully done. Um, a
few things to highlight. You have your
vinyl [music] plank throughout the home.
No carpet. I know that's a big deal for
a lot of people. All of the selections
are super modernized [music] and
updated, including fixtures. the uh gray
[music] taupish walls. I just think it's
really pretty and I think you can really
tell even just from looking at it on
[music] picture or video. Let's go take
a look at the kitchen.
Now, this kitchen is so pretty. It's
very open. Um you can really do a a lot
in this space. You have this wonderful
center prep island and then everything
overlooks into [music] the main living
space. And when they made the
selections, they made sure to keep
everything again very modern. It's very
cool [music] toned and it just feels
really great in here. You have these
stunning granite countertops, off-white,
gray, custom cabinets with the shaker
style, the squared uh stainless steel
appliances,
and again, really pretty overlooking
[music]
into the living space. Let's go.
Okay, I'm kind of weird about this. I
don't know why I think it's so cool, but
I really love when builders incorporate
stonework into homes. It's not super
common, but I think it makes properties
look super elegant. [music] So, you can
see this builder incorporated a lot of
the um stonework highlighting around the
kitchen, which ties into the stonework
of the fireplace. I don't know. I just
really really love it. In fact, if I
ever build a home again, I'll definitely
be doing something [music] like that.
Love to hear what you think in the
comments below. Do you love that? Do you
love that style? Do you hate it? But
either way, I think this home is just so
tastefully done. It's so pretty, and I
hope you love it, too. You'll love the
master suite, a true retreat with a
walk-in shower, soaking tub, dual
vanities, and a fantastic closet with so
much storage. It's a [music] split floor
plan, so the guest bedrooms are a great
size and tucked away for privacy.
Perfect for families, visitors, or even
a home office [music] setup. The main
living room is cozy and inviting with a
stunning large [music] sliding glass
door that expands your living space
right outdoors.
Outside, you've got a grill and outdoor
kitchen setup. And this massive halfacre
lot gives you room to breathe with
mature trees just behind the property
line, so there's no feeling of being on
top of your neighbors. And of course,
the laundry space is even more
functional with a great amount of
cabinets for storage, a utility sink,
and folding station. [music] Thanks for
joining me on this property tour today.
I hope you found it helpful. And if you
are relocating to the central Texas
area, whether that's Temple, [music]
Belton, Celo, or any of the surrounding
areas, maybe you're just looking for an
upgrade from your current situation. I'd
love to be [music] your resource. You
can also head on over to
livinginctx.com.
That's my website. I have some really,
really fantastic [music]
resources including relocation guides,
map tours, things of that nature. And
don't forget to like, subscribe, [music]
and click the bell notification so that
you can stay up to date on all things
real estate here in Central Texas. Till
next time.